<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Pine Grove Interactive</title><link>https://pgi.dev/</link><description>AI &amp; Data Engineering expertise</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>kristoffer@pgi.dev (Kristoffer Johansson)</managingEditor><webMaster>kristoffer@pgi.dev (Kristoffer Johansson)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 09:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pgi.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Supervised learning creates more value than generative AI</title><link>https://pgi.dev/supervised-learning-is-valuable/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate><author>Kristoffer Johansson</author><guid>https://pgi.dev/supervised-learning-is-valuable/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>What gives you a greater competitive advantage than generative AI, language models, RAG &amp; agents?</p>
<blockquote>
<p><strong><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supervised_learning" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Supervised learning</a>
</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="the-value-of-supervised-learning">The value of supervised learning</h2>
<p>A lot of attention and resources are being directed toward the previously mentioned buzzwords, but remember that the real, significant value lies in supervised learning.</p>
<p>In the graphic below, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrewyng/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Andrew Ng</a>
 illustrates different areas of AI. We see generative AI, which has been the hot topic for the past two years, but also supervised learning, unsupervised learning, and reinforcement learning—three fundamental pillars of machine learning. The size of the circles indicates the current value of these areas and how much Andrew predicts they will grow over the next three years.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Developer experience matters a lot</title><link>https://pgi.dev/developer-experience-matters-a-lot/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><author>Kristoffer Johansson</author><guid>https://pgi.dev/developer-experience-matters-a-lot/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>In order for develovers to be succ.. 🚧🚨 Developers needs a.. 🚧🚨</p>
<p>Ugh! It&rsquo;s no fun to be interrupted when you are just getting started.</p>
<h2 id="why-does-it-feel-like-an-obstacle-course">Why does it feel like an obstacle course?</h2>
<p>This is what the developer experience (DevEx) feels like in many larger, long-established organizations with significant technical debt. Add to that the constant pinging of chat windows and overflowing inboxes, and you’ve got a recipe for sluggish deliveries and frustrated developers!</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Services in AI &amp; Data Engineering</title><link>https://pgi.dev/offer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><author>Kristoffer Johansson</author><guid>https://pgi.dev/offer/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>We leverage our expertise in AI and data engineering to make your business more efficient. Whether you already have a data team or are just starting out, we provide the resources you need to succeed with your data projects.</p>
<h2 id="upskilling-in-ai--machine-learning">Upskilling in AI &amp; Machine Learning</h2>
<p>Our experts provide tailored training programs to equip you and your developers with the skills needed to work effectively with AI and machine learning. The education package offers hands-on workshops, practical guidance, and actionable insights designed to address your business needs.</p>]]></description></item></channel></rss>